so hello everybody I'm coming you to you from Firewell Lake I just got the boat
out of storage and taking it so the next section you're working on is about
clocks about circuits that are clocked it's about timing the timing is it's
spring it's time to get the boat out clock stuff may seem a little bit weird
to you it has to do with as circuits get longer and more complex we to predict
the output to make sure we don't have tiny errors creeping in we have to wait
until the circuit stabilizes and everything you've seen so far everything
seems instant but nothing is really instant and so clocks has to do with
measuring sort of the worst-case propagation delay and setting a clock
rate and using the clock rate or certain values to stabilize to a zero or a one
and then we grab them okay so this section is a little weird but it's an
essential part of computers an essential part of the fetch execute cycle and
then we're going to after this we're going to work into the fetch execute
cycle cheers